Narrator: 1
Your lifestyle
A: What do you usually do in the morning?
How do you relax?
What did you do last weekend?
Narrator: 2
Your home
B: What’s your favorite room in your home?
Are you neat or messy?
Did you do a lot of housework last week?
Narrator: 3
Your abilities
A: What languages can you speak?
Can you sing or play a musical instrument?
Why are you learning English?
Narrator: 4
Your places
B: What’s your favorite place to spend the weekend?
Where did you go for your last vacation?
Where are you going to go for your next vacation?
Narrator: 5
Your tastes
A: What’s your favorite time of year?
What book are you reading right now?
What kind of TV shows do you like watching?
Narrator: 6
Your experiences
What movies have you seen recently?
What’s the most beautiful place you’ve ever been to?
Have you ever been to the US or Britain?